A Guide to the Virginia Room Biography Files, Undated
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Pickett, George Edward, Civil War General
- Pinkett Family
- Plaskett Family
- Plaskett, Susan Annie
- Platt, Charles M.
- Plissner, Lenore
- Plum, Kenneth R., 1941-?
- Pocahontas, ?-1617
- Podesta Family
- Poe, Edgar Allan, 1809-1849
- Pohanka, Brian C., ?-2005
- Poland, Lawrence
- Pollard, John G. Jr.
- Poling, Harold A. "Red", Ford Motor Company executive, 1925-2012
- Pond, Glen D.
- Porter, Carl W.
- Porter Family
- Powell, Lewis F. Jr.
- Preston Family
- Price, Keith
- Price, Murriel F.
- Price, Stanley G.
- Prichard, Edgar Allen, ?-2000
- Prichard, Nancy Montague McCandlish, ?-2006
- Pruefer, Cliff, 1915-?
- Pryor, Henry
- Pugh, Evelyn L., ?-1987
- Pugh, John R., ?-1891
- Puller, Linda T. "Toddy", Va. Senate
- Pulley, Mary Grace Watt, 1918-2011
- Pulsipher, Bill
- Putnam, Carleton
- Quander Family
- Quenstedt, Warren B.
- Rae, Jimmy, ?-2006
- Ragsdale, Ben Jr.
- Rainwater, Thelma May, ?-2009
- Randall, Robert L.
- Randolph Family
- Randolph, Robert B.
- Ransom, Candace, 1952-?
- Rappleyea, Millard C.
- Ratcliffe Family
- Rawlings Family
- Rawlings, George C. Jr.
- Ray, Charles, ?-1982
- Reardon Family
- Reed, Walter, 1851-?
- Reese, Gary
- Reeves-Graybell Family
- Register Family
- Register, Ethel Wilcox, Clerk of the Board
- Rehder, Mark Clifford, ?-2000
- Reiber, Paul
- Reid Family
- Reid, Robert H., Director, GMU (1963-1966)
- Reilly, William K.
- Rems, Alan
- Remsburg, Vera B.
- Renzi, Eugene Carmen, ?-2008
- Rhee, Jhoon
- Ribble, John F. III
- Ricci, Barbara Guignon, Author
- Richards, Amos
- Richards, Lilla, BOS, Dranesville Dist.
- Richardson Family
- Richardson, David, Author
- Richardson, Frederick Wilmer, 1853-1936
- Richardson, Malcolm L. "Rich", Archeologist, Historian, Library Volunteer, 1929-2006
- Riddle, Hugh, Jr.
- Rieger, Donie C., McLean Resident; Local Historian, 1912-1996
- Rierson, Michael
- Rigg, Shirley
- Rigg, Townley
- Ring, Constance K., 1932-1997
- Ritchie, F. Carbery
- Rittenhouse, E. Stanley
- Rives-Kroehebuehl Family
- Robb Family
- Robb, Charles F., 1939-?
- Robbins, Routh M., ?-1993
- Robertson Pat
- Robertson, A. Willis
- Robertson, Elvin W. "Robbie", Aviator, Founder of Hylba Valley Airport, 1902-1979
- Robertson, John Graham "Gray"
- Robey Family
- Robinson Family
- Robinson, Charles A., Jr., Mayor, Town of Vienna
- Robinson, Clarence J., ?-1983
- Robinson, Frederick W., Herndon Businessman, 1888-1972
- Robinson, George S., Author
- Robinson, Maud
- Rockwell, George Lincoln, American Nazi Party Chief (Murdered 1967), ?-1967
- Rodio, Pat
- Roebuck Family
- Rogers, Edith, BOS, Dranesville Dist., 1914-1979
- Rohrer, David M., Chief, Fairfax County Police Department
- Rolfe, John, 1585-1622
- Rose Family
- Rose, Robert
- Rosen, Judith
- Rothrock, Thomas J.
- Rowland, Florence
- Rubinowitz, Arthurea Brown
- Ruck, F. Lee, County Attorney, 1940-?
- Rudd, Margaret Thomas, Author
- Ruffing, L. Fred
- Ruffner, William Henry, 1824-?
- Rumsey, James, 1743-1792
- Russell, John
- Russell, Robert Cecil, 1929-2013
- Russell, Walter
- Rust, Jeanne Johnson, 1919-?
- Rust, John H. Sr., Attorney
- Rust, John W.
- Ruzicka, Gregory, ?-2004
- Ryder, Richard J.
- Sahr, Morris G.
- Salak, Phylis, Voter Registrar, City of Fairfax
- Sanders, Milburn, Historian, 1922-?
- Sanders, Robert Alexander, Narcotics Detective, 1873-1947
- Sangster Family
- Sansone, Cordelia Grantham, ?-2007
- Saslaw, Richard, 1940-?
- Satterfield, David E., III
- Saunders Family
- Scannell, Thomas Patrick, Catholic priest, 1910-2005
- Schar, Dwight C.
- Scheel, Eugene, Cartographer
- Schneider, Eugene
- Schorer, Lonnie
- Schreiner-Yantis, Netti
- Schumann, Herbert
- Scott, James M., 1938-?
- Scott, Richard Marshall, Owner of "Bush Hill", 1770-1833
- Scott, Willard
- Scott, William L., 1915-?
- Scott, Winfield, 1786-1866
- Sebastian, Benjamin, 1739-1832
- Sebben, James
- Seeley Family
- Seeley, Martha Ulfelder, ?-2002
- Seeley, Rudolph, Developer, 1906-1988
- Seeman, Madena Jane, ?-2014
- Segman, Ralph
- Selement, Joan, Author
- Senese, Donald Joseph, ?-2004
- Sewall Family
- Shacochis, Helen Mary, ?-2005
- Shacochis, John
- Shafran, George
- Shands, Nancy Lamb
- Shanholtzer Family
- Sharp, L. Harold, ?-1978
- Sharp, Madeline Holt, 1907-1998
- Sharper Family
- Shaw, Harold M., ?-1999
- Sheads Family
- Shelton Family
- Shepherd, William Thomas
- Sheppard, William Ludwell, Artist, 1833-1912
- Sherman Family
- Sherwood Family
- Shirley, Henry G., 1875-1941
- Shiver, Jube Burrell, 1922-2010
- Shlesinger, B. Edward, Jr.
- Shockey Family
- Shortridge Family
- Shouse, Catherine Filene
- Shreve Family
- Shreve, George William, 1844-1940
- Shupe, Charles
- Shur, Lee C.
- Sickles, Merrill, Jr.
- Simmons Family
- Simon, Robert E. Jr., 1914-?
- Simons, Vera
- Simpson Family
- Sinclair, Arthur W.
- Siple, Paul
- Sisson Family
- Sizemore, Christine C., 1927-?
- Skibiak, David Paul, Artist
- Skinner Family
- Skipwith, Jean Miller, 1748-1826
- Skorupski, Jean
- Slane Family
- Slaughter, Robert Madison, 1857-?
- Smith Family
- Smith, Alson H.
- Smith, Andrew, ?-1978
- Smith, Darryl C.
- Smith, H. Selwyn
- Smith, Howard W., 1883-1976
- Smith, Jeanette
- Smith, John, 1580-1631
- Smith, Joshua, Author
- Smith, Stanley Warren, 1927-2003
- Smith, Verlin W, ?-2007
- Smith, Vernon L., Nobel Laureate
- Smith, William "Extra Billy", 1796-1887
- Smitherman, Smythman, Smotherman Family
- Smoot Family
- Smyth, Linda Q., BOS, Providence Dist.
- Snyder, George T., 1940-?
- Spann, Barbara Towner, ?-2001
- Sparacio, Ruth L., 1917-2007
- Sparacio, Sam, ?-2000
- Speh, Francis J., 1916-?
- Spicer, James Albert, 1844-1948
- Spillane, Robert R.
- Spindle, Robert Leachman, 1840-1923
- Spong, William B. Jr., 1920-?
- Spotswood, Alexander, 1676-1740
- Springston, Sterling E., ?-2001
- Sprissler, Kathleen, Author
- Sprouse, Edith Moore, Author; Mount Vernon Resident; Local Historian, 1923-2004
- Spurling Family
- Stalcup Family
- Stambaugh, Warren G.
- Stanhagen, William H., 1928-?
- Stanley, Thomas Bahnson, Virginia Governor, ?-1970
- Starr, Nicholas
- Steadman, Rev. Melvin Lee, 1932-1987
- Steel, Thomas
- Steele, Sidney R.
- Stevens, Donald C.
- Stewart Family
- Stickman, Ralph
- Stillwell, Nicholas
- Stinnette, Edward L., Chief, Fairfax County Fire Department
- Stone, Kathryn H., ?-1995
- Stone, Ormond, 1847-1933
- Strickhouser, Donald E.
- Stringfellow, Benjamin Franklin, 1840-1913
- Stroop Family
- Stryker Family
- Stuart, James Ewell Brown, 1833-1864
- Stuber, Robert, 1956-?
- Stull, C. Meade
- Stuntz, Mayo & Constance, Authors; Vienna Residents; Local Historians
- Suddarth Family
- Sullivan, Mary Arneita, ?-1974
- Sullivan, Rosemari
- Sully, Thomas, Artist, 1783-?
- Summers Family
- Sundquist, Beth Ritchie, 1916-1982
- Sutherland, David A., 1930-?
- Sutherland, Marvin M., 1912-?
- Sutphin Family
- Sutton, Myron D., Author
- Swayze, Roy
- Sweig, Donald M.
- Swinson, James D., 1913-?
- Syphax Family
- Tanzer, Lester, Author
- Tart, Nelson M.
- Tate, James R., 1943-?
- Taylor Family
- Temple, Pick
- Templeman, Eleanor Lee, 1906-1990
- Terrett, George H.
- Terrett, Washington
- Thackrey, Jessie, 1913-2013
- Thaler, William J., 1925-?
- Thoburn, Robert L., 1929-?
- Thomas Family
- Thomas, Alvin Leroy
- Thomas, Henry Wirt, Judge-Lt. Gov., 1812-1890
- Thomas, Sonya K.
- Thomas, William Griffith
- Thompson Family
- Thompson, Lorin A., Chancellor, GMU (1966-1973)
- Thorman, Rose
- Thornton Family
- Thorowgood Family
- Thout, Pierre, NASA Astronaut
- Tibbets, Jean, ?-2004
- Tilp, Frederick, Historian-Author, 1908-1988
- Timanus, Eddie
- Tingstrum, James Frederick, Jr., Photographer, ?-2007
- Todd, James W.
- Tolbert Family
- Tolers Family
- Torrey Family
- Townsend Family
- Trammell Family
- Trapnell, Christine R.
- Travesky, Marie
- Traynor, Andrew, Capt., U. S. Army: Medal of Honor Recipient, 1843-1920
- Treiber, Kenneth L., Author, Inventor
- Trible, Paul S. Jr., 1947-?
- Triplett Family
- Troth, Jacob M., 1828-1915
- Trott, Samuel, 1784-1866
- Troy, Anthony F.
- Tuck, William M., 1897-1983
- Tugwell, Ron
- Tull, Ronald I.
- Tunnell, William
- Turberville Family, also Pettit; Thornton; DeBell
- Turley Family
- Turpin Family
- Tussey Family
- Tuthill, Warren E., Sr., ?-2006
- Tyers Family
- Tyler, Robert H.
- Ulfelder, Ethel Housel, ?-1969
- Ungaro, Justine, Photographer
- Utterback Family
- Valentine, Drew
- Valentine, Edward Virginius, Sculpter
- Van Metre Family
- Van Metre, Albert G., Developer, ?-2008
- Van Voorhees Family
- Vandivier, Robert Carroll, ?-2007
- VanDyck, E. Calvin, Judge, 1915-1967
- Vaughan, Sue Landon
- Vickery, Clarise
- Vickery, Raymond E. Jr., 1942-?
- Victor, John
- Viguerie, Richard Art
- Villar, Elizabeth David, Historian, ?-2002
- Von Egger, Joan B., ?-2010
- Vondersmith, Fletcher Stulen, 1922-1997
- Waddell, Charles, Va. Senate
- Wagner, Charles R. "Chappie", Architect, ?-2007
- Walke Family
- Walker, Fred W.
- Walker, Jay
- Walker, Robert B., FCPS Administrator, ?-1974
- Walker, Rosa Lee, ?-2003
- Wall, Charles Cecil, 1903-1995
- Wallace, Barbara Brooks, Author
- Walsh, Ray
- Walsh, Raymond V., Jr., 1936-?
- Waple, George Henry, III, 1921-2010
- Warden Family
- Warfield, James A.
- Warner, John
- Warner, Mark
- Warren, Rita, 1928-?
- Washington Family
- Washington Family - Homes
- Washington, George, 1732-1799
- Washington, Martha, 1731-1802
- Watters, Frank C.
- Watters, William, ?-1827
- Watts, Lawrence M., 1924-1970
- Watts, Vivian
- Webb Family
- Webb, Earnest E., McLean Resident, 1888-1975
- Webb, Jim
- Webdale, Walter Downes
- Weems, W. L.
- Weickhardt, Karl F.
- Weisiger, Eileen M., ?-2001
- Weiss, Barbara
- Welsh, Thomas Jerome, First Bishop of Diocese of Arlington, 1921-?
- Wenzel Family
- Wessel, Theodore J.
- West Family
- West, William A., 1874-1978
- Wheelan, Belle, NVCC President
- Wheeler Family
- Wheeler, William
- White Family
- White, Winnie
- Whitehouse, Joseph, Member, Lewis & Clark Expedition
- Whitley Family
- Whitman, Merrill Joseph, 1919-2008
- Whitmore, George, ?-1850
- Whitmore, Harold B., ?-1973
- Whorton, Leonard L., 1937-?
- Wiehle, Carl Adolph Max, Founder, Town of Wiehle, Va.
- Wilder, L. Douglass, 1931-?
- Wiley, Robert, ?-1932
- Wilhelmi, Charlotte
- Wilkins, Anne A., 1914-1996
- Wilkinson Family
- Wilkinson, Joyce E.
- Willcoxon Family
- Williams Family
- Williams, Carrington, 1919-?
- Williams, Susan, 2004 Olympic triathlon bronze medallist
- Williams, Taylor M., FCPS Superintendent
- Willis, Albert Gallatin, ?-1864
- Wilson, Jane Smoot, ?-1987
- Wilson, Laurie Frost
- Wilson, Robert W., 1933-?
- Winfield, Louise, Author
- Winslow, Joan, Author
- Winsor, Christopher
- Winter, Helen
- Wirt, William, ?-1834
- Wissler, Nettie Lou
- Witt Family
- Wojtum, Lily
- Wolf, Frank R.
- Wolff, Tobias, Author
- Wood, John C., Mayor, City of Fairfax, 1918-1994
- Woods, Jane
- Woods, Thomas H.
- Woodson, Wilbert Tucker, Superintendant of Schools (1929-1961), 1893-1982
- Woody, Oscar S., Crew Member, S. S. Titanic, ?-1911
- Wrench, William B.
- Wrenn, James, 1728-1815
- Wright Family
- Wright, Thomas B., BOS, Providence District, ?-1991
- Wyatt, Edward, City Manager, City of Fairfax
- Yeonas, Constantine G. "Gus", Developer, ?-1990
- Young, Lehman, Fairfax Resident, 1916-?
- Young, Nathaniel, Mayor, City of Fairfax
- Yowell Family
- Zimmer Family
- Zimmer, Carl L.
- Zissios, Patricia
- Zollman, William M. Jr., City Manager, City of Fairfax